<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-08-09T19:43:39+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">younglink4.github.io</title><subtitle>Some young one's thoughts</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Anti Damone</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Anti-Damone/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Anti Damone" /><published>2017-08-09T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Anti-Damone</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Anti-Damone/">&lt;div class=&quot;jekyll-twitter-plugin&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;sv&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;jekyll-twitter-plugin (1.0.0): A Liquid tag plugin for Jekyll that renders Tweets from Twitter API &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.co/m4EIQPM9h4&quot;&gt;http://t.co/m4EIQPM9h4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; RubyGems (@rubygems) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/rubygems/status/518821243320287232&quot;&gt;October 5, 2014&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;fss&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;jekyll-twitter-plugin&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The literature ITSELF was hostile m&amp;#39;dude. Hostile literature is covered in most company HR policies. How are you so ignorant of this? &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/7cTRdOWldn&quot;&gt;https://t.co/7cTRdOWldn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Twink Peaks (@RealDorianDawes) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RealDorianDawes/status/894752724318797825&quot;&gt;August 8, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sowieso nicht lol
https://twitter.com/aanand/status/894741503570063361
https://twitter.com/der_Grobi/status/894746393453051906
https://twitter.com/susanthesquark/status/894740662884614144
https://twitter.com/ashleyfeinberg/status/894758234363486208
https://twitter.com/der_Grobi/status/894755968986136576
https://twitter.com/RealDorianDawes/status/894754651236483072&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">jekyll-twitter-plugin (1.0.0): A Liquid tag plugin for Jekyll that renders Tweets from Twitter API http://t.co/m4EIQPM9h4&amp;mdash; RubyGems (@rubygems) October 5, 2014 fss The literature ITSELF was hostile m&amp;#39;dude. Hostile literature is covered in most company HR policies. How are you so ignorant of this? https://t.co/7cTRdOWldn&amp;mdash; Twink Peaks (@RealDorianDawes) August 8, 2017 Sowieso nicht lol https://twitter.com/aanand/status/894741503570063361 https://twitter.com/der_Grobi/status/894746393453051906 https://twitter.com/susanthesquark/status/894740662884614144 https://twitter.com/ashleyfeinberg/status/894758234363486208 https://twitter.com/der_Grobi/status/894755968986136576 https://twitter.com/RealDorianDawes/status/894754651236483072</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Least self-aware aka the Antifa</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Least-Self-Aware-the-Antifa/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Least self-aware aka the Antifa" /><published>2017-08-08T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-08T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Least-Self-Aware-the-Antifa</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Least-Self-Aware-the-Antifa/">&lt;p&gt;If I were to award annual prizes, then I think I had a clear winner for at least one of them, every year. The political left is just at the top of the game when it comes to being unself-aware.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://twitter.com/jobhaver/status/894227204858576902&quot; alt=&quot;Yet this tweet shows perfectly well, how good they're at it&quot; /&gt;. It even has 200 retweets and 500 likes by the time I write this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It always feels like they never heard of the streisand effect, although this is a bit different. Usually it says to better keep your mouth shut about something that you don’t want to see published, since making deal out of it will only shift more attention towards it. In this case, it’s rather how they can’t fathom different opinions and the fact, that their action will bring a reaction. Historically, many movements gave birth to a counter-movement. Or an action was followed by a reaction. In the the second half of the 18th century the Age of “Sturm und Drang” in Germany came only to existence because literature at that time was dominated by the Age of Enlightenment. During Hitler’s rise many counter-movements, such as the anti-fascist action itself, sprung up to oppose him. This goes on and on, because we don’t have the same mentality, opinion or priorities. Just because you think your actions are legitimate doesn’t mean someone else does. Not even if they agree with your views.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the main problems here is, that antifas attack what &lt;em&gt;they&lt;/em&gt; deem fascist. So if they think Trump supporters help a fascist, they could rally against them. However, the people themselves are likely not fascists. Trump may even be one, but if you rally against them, you attack &lt;em&gt;them&lt;/em&gt; not Trump. You attack their right to gather march for their political believe. Since these supporters think they’re right, they will dismiss these antifascists as violent. From their perspective, it’s an attack on them. Of course this is also shown in the media repeatedly, so those who don’t align with the antifa’s views, will be against them. An anti-antifa so to speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s even more amazing about this, is the fact that antifa is very much authorian themselves. They want to dictate what which opinion is right and which one is wrong. They want to decide what can be said and discussed and what can’t. This is inheritly authorian, even if they want to shut down nazis exclusively. That’s because you have to identify nazis first. That’s already bad enough, since there’s no way to draw a clear line anyway. On top of that, you can’t know what a person will say before they say it. So even if you manage to determine what is racist and what who is racist, you can’t just forbid them to voice their opinion. That would simultaneously mean a nazi can’t talk about climate change or economy anymore, because he’s racist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another trait that fits to the authorian picture is their view on violence. There’s a good reason why the government has a monopoly on violence in democracies. Any other form of violence that does not follow a set, transparent law will foster fear. It is by definition arbitary, since no one knows what others think or how they react. Antifascists now argue, that violence is neccessary against certain views. Anyone else can’t follow their line of thought though, so it’s unclear who is a target to them and who isn’t. Earlier this year, antifas argued that it’s okay to punch nazis, because it’s self-defense. Because nazis are gonna cause harm to others, it’s perfectly fine to harm them first. Now, if we follow this logic, it can be reversed too. The tweet above implies, that the author of the article is a fascist in the eyes of certain people. Since I agree with the article, I could’ve technically written it similarly, so I’d be a fascist in their eyes too. And well, since antifas are against fascists obviously and don’t have any qualms to resort to violence, following their logic, it’d be perfectly fine for me to get the first hit in. To make it worse, I don’t even know who wants me harm and who doesn’t unless they come at me with their raised. But in that case, I don’t even need such a logic to come to that conclusion, so this logic fails in itself. It fails even more at resolving the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And so the award for the least self-aware group in the United States of America goes to… the Antifascist Action! Congratulations&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2017/09/the-rise-of-the-violent-left/534192/?&quot; alt=&quot;In case the tweet doesn't exist anymore for whatever reason, here a link to the article&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">If I were to award annual prizes, then I think I had a clear winner for at least one of them, every year. The political left is just at the top of the game when it comes to being unself-aware.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Google employee</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Google-Employee/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Google employee" /><published>2017-08-08T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-08T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Google-Employee</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Google-Employee/">&lt;p&gt;A Google employee is talking about Google’s &lt;img src=&quot;http://gizmodo.com/exclusive-heres-the-full-10-page-anti-diversity-screed-1797564320&quot; alt=&quot;political agenda&quot; /&gt;. It’s quite interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But really, why don’t people just lay back and let things happen. You don’t need to force things. If women don’t wanna go into tech that much, then you don’t have many women in tech. It’s a shame but not such a big problem.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A Google employee is talking about Google’s . It’s quite interesting.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Privilege</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Privilege/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Privilege" /><published>2017-08-04T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-04T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Privilege</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Privilege/">&lt;p&gt;This is basically a follow up from the last post. An Iowan student newspaper published an article about &lt;img src=&quot;http://daily-iowan.com/2017/07/25/williams-what-is-privilege-and-what-do-we-do-with-it/&quot; alt=&quot;privilege&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The article is all kinds of stupid, peaking at the “cognitive privilege”, but at its core, it still fits at what I explained earlier, so why not take it apart?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The relevant notion of privilege I define as the receipt of certain benefits wholly through accident of birth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is interesting in this case, since the author, Williams, is also talking about white privilege there. He may want to say being white is nothing but advantegeous, but this is the line of thinking that leads to racism. Color does not grant you anything others couldn’t achieve the same way. I’m aware the US is still more racist than most other countries on this side of the Atlantic, but it’s not so extreme, that it will stop your career in the tracks. Blacks, too, can go to school, as bad as it is, graduate, go to college, pay high fees, and eventually hit off well. They can also fail in the process or luck out with a good idea. None of this has much to do with skin color though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There are many kinds of privilege besides white privilege: cognitive privilege, for example. We now know that intelligence is not something we have significant control over but is something we are born with. We are living in a society in which success is increasingly linked to one’s intelligence. This is not to say that intelligence is the only factor that is important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course intelligence is a deciding factor for success and parts of it are linked to birth, yes. John Stuart Mill would’ve never started off as the genius child he is, if his father didn’t have a huge library he could basically devour in his early years. It fostered his already existent potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;But when doing so, we must also bear in mind the purpose of drawing attention to privileges. The purpose is not to instill a sort of Catholic guilt in someone’s psyche, nor is it an excuse to make oneself feel better by demonizing another. The purpose of pointing out someone’s privilege is to remind them of the infinite number of experiences that are possible and the very large number of experiences that are actual that they know very little about. The purpose is to enlarge their moral consciousness, to make them more sympathetic to people who are less fortunate than they are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me some of this privilege babbling sounds more like an excuse for your own failure. “He’s just smarter than me, it’s no wonder he doing better than me.” or “Well, he was born white, naturally he’d end up on top of me.” don’t really increase your self-esteem. We need challenges to overcome ourselves. To go back to Mill, he didn’t become a genius just through by being smart, he actually had to read hundreds, thousands of books to acquire the knowledge he later used. The same goes for Gauß or other mathematicians. They sat down and calculated for hours, days, weeks, months to come to the conclusions that made them famous. Seriously, Gauß didn’t have a calculator, so he had to go through his calculations over and over again for more than half a year, using tens of thousands pieces of paper in the process. That’s the sort of dedication you need for real success. It doesn’t come “naturally” to those who are born “privileged”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Feelings of guilt are natural when coming to consciousness of one’s place in the scheme of things — and noticing that one has been conferred benefits through sheer accident — but guilt is an impediment to social-justice action, not a motivator (guilt slides easily into resentment). Keeping the general notion of “privilege” in mind allows us to notice that there are different species of privilege. We can debate whether “whiteness” is a sort of “master privilege” that overrules all others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And lastly, don’t guilt trip people for no reason. I don’t and never will feel guilty over my birth. I’m lucky enough to not be born into poverty or a family of abusive, irresponsible parents, yes. But that shouldn’t be seen as something to feel guilty about. It should rather be seen as the norm and not something to feel negative about. Likewise, why should it be a bad thing to be born off well? Even if you raise awareness of those who were lucky, what does it help them? Yeah, they had a pretty simple life, they’re well off, but they can’t change anything about it either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It certainly doesn’t help that the left’s goals, motivations and reasons are all over the place. While this fellow doesn’t want to demonize whites and intellectuals, others do exactly that. Another group guilt trips whites. Yet they have very similar views, so they mix up in some twisted mindset that contradicts itself. Thinking about it, that’s pretty interesting in itself.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This is basically a follow up from the last post. An Iowan student newspaper published an article about</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Other left</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Other-Left/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Other left" /><published>2017-08-04T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-04T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Other-Left</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Other-Left/">&lt;p&gt;I think I’m starting to understand why I loathe the “other left”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean fundamentally, they’re pretty close to my believes. They also want equality, education for everyone, are against big corporations. Yet there’s also a fundamental difference and I think I can put my finger on that. To illustrate, here’s a &lt;img src=&quot;https://twitter.com/RealDorianDawes/status/893155181621387264&quot; alt=&quot;tweet&quot; /&gt; of someone who qualifies as part of that group. The tweets around it put it into context, but that one alone practically show the difference between us. 
What I mainly mean is the racist part. Capitalism isn’t racist, it’s just problematic. I share the idea of capitalism being way to predominant in this world, absolutely. Single individuals or even certain groups shouldn’t be able to exert as much power as they do with their money. See for example Soros or &lt;img src=&quot;https://www.thenation.com/article/goldmans-greek-gambit/&quot; alt=&quot;Goldman Sachs&quot; /&gt; who can influence countries. But even on a smaller scale, lobbyists heavily influence politicians whereas common folk have nothing. 
But capitalism isn’t racist. Looking at Europe more than 100 years back, it already existed and extremely profitable for the rich. Those who owned capital could determine who gets work and who doesn’t. It was a completely onesided display of power, even though it was a lot more homogenous than it is now. Capitalists don’t care about skincolor, not at all. All they want is success. That’s the nature of a successful person who made it big. Thinking otherwise leads to very different conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Incidentally, I also don’t think capitalism is THE evil of the world. Capitalism and democracy both shape our western world, yet they both have fundamental flaws in their current state. Democracy only represents a few, not the majority. Capitalism at its core leads to very badly distributed wealth. Yet we don’t have good alternatives. Money in itself is a good tool to trade goods. And I honestly think capitalism could work out in some way, albeit very regulated. Financial capitalism would need to be abolished altogether or at least made unprofitable. Banks in general should be a lot more regulated to not lend out money as they want to generate more. And so on&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, there’s still the main problem with that line of thought like I described above: It doesn’t lead to equality. Currently the popular political believe is that of the evil white man who ruled for way too long, so we need others in power now. To have diversity. Let them be black, female, disabled, trans, gay. It doesn’t matter as long as they aren’t cis, white and male. They don’t even need to be president, other high positions are also accomplishments. They completely disregard political diversity. Well not completely, even they didn’t wanted to see the warmongering Hillary Clinton in office. Yet these very people celebrate every time a “special” person accomplishes something, as if their sexuality has something to do with it. Sure I want to live in a world where sexuality doesn’t interfere with your career, much like I don’t want the church to interfere with politics. But forcing it isn’t good either. It’s racist, sexist, ablist, etc. Exactly what they’re trying to fight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This fight for the underdog is sickening. Helping those you deem oppressed only helps those you deem oppressed, of course. That left only thinks of good guys vs bad guys. They’re the obvious good guys, flawless in their views, others are the bad guys. Those who are oppressed need to helped. They completely miss out on the fact, that they need to identify these first. To identify them, they need to specify who is oppressed. So first you claim who is oppressed, then you identify those, then you help them. That’s exactly what I hate about that idea. It’s not really about equality, otherwise you’d just help just about anyone who needs help. It’s like telling a young white boy with alcoholic parents living in poverty “I’m sorry, we don’t have any programs for you, we can’t help you”. Just because he fits the same criteria as Trump, Bush, Gates, etc. doesn’t mean he’s as well off as them. (Mind you, it’s also mind-boggling how women who take up more than half the population are deemed oppressed. I doubt many of them feel actively oppressed in the western world.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extending an arm to those in need is what brings equality. It’s the very thing Jesus did. He helped others indiscriminately, not based on sex, origin or whether they were missing a limb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that all is pretty much the difference between my equality to theirs. Theirs is a more authorian approach, since someone has to determine whether a group is (still) oppressed or not. Praising and glorifying those who accomplished something “despite” being a women, black person, etc also implies that it is to be expected from those who aren’t of those categories. Say a girl comes out on the top of her year in mathematics, she’d be praised for that. But in the first place, she can only be praised for that, because it’s seen as a boys thing. Her accomplishment in itself isn’t any more praiseworthy as that of the boys before her, every year.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I think I’m starting to understand why I loathe the “other left”.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Transgender gene</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Transgender-Gene/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Transgender gene" /><published>2017-08-03T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-03T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Transgender-Gene</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Transgender-Gene/">&lt;p&gt;Reading &lt;img src=&quot;http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-lgbt-biology-idUSKBN1AJ0F0&quot; alt=&quot;this artcile by Reuters&quot; /&gt; something weird came up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m all for research before action. It’s basically “think before you act” on a bigger scale, the scale of politics. So I welcome such a research before decisions are made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;That quest has made some transgender people nervous. If a “cause” is found it could posit a “cure,” potentially opening the door to so-called reparative therapies similar to those that attempt to turn gay people straight, advocates say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many genetic diseases can we cure again? Autism? Down-syndrome? Dementia? We’re still practically defenseless against genetics, so I don’t see that worry. Being transgender isn’t even a hindrance per se.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;One-third of transgender people reported a negative healthcare experience in the previous year such as verbal harassment, refusal of treatment or the need to teach their doctors about transgender care, according to a landmark survey of nearly 28,000 people released last year by the National Center for Transgender Equality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verbal harassment is a no-go, refusal of treatment shouldn’t happen regularly either, but needing to teach doctors about transgender care? We have gynecologists who specialize in women, exactly because we need such specialists for some cases. What do you exepct? Transgender isn’t that common, that every doctor in the country knows his or her share on the topic. Medicine is a wide field, so wide that it needs many different specialists to treat correctly. Doctors also hold a lot of responsibility. That’s why it’s foolish to assume every doctor will help you. Doctors are allowed to refuse treatment because of that. They should be. That is of course if it doesn’t fall under his or her specialty. A hospital refusing a wounded would be a scandal under normal circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Reading something weird came up.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">German Cabaret</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/German-Cabaret/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="German Cabaret" /><published>2017-06-24T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-06-24T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/German-Cabaret</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/German-Cabaret/">&lt;p&gt;It’s such a shame I can almost never recommend German Cabaret to my internation friends. Some of it manages to be the perfect mix of humour and critique on the ruling class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SG0Ql0VfcRg&amp;amp;t=3s&quot; alt=&quot;Look at Volker Pispers for example&quot; /&gt;. A truly knowledgable man, showing us the the problems of our time. Even this one, performed 14 years ago, still stays relevant. His ability to predict some events is almost scary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also a shame there isn’t an English equivalent. Nothing goes really deep into the political structure. Basically all the criticism that comes around, can be compared to the daily show: Superficial, mainly making fun of the politicians.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It’s such a shame I can almost never recommend German Cabaret to my internation friends. Some of it manages to be the perfect mix of humour and critique on the ruling class.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Istanbul Convention</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Istanbul-Convention/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Istanbul Convention" /><published>2017-06-10T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-06-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Istanbul-Convention</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Istanbul-Convention/">&lt;p&gt;Latvia isn’t gonna sign a new convention &lt;img src=&quot;http://eng.lsm.lv/article/society/society/justice-ministry-advice-says-latvia-should-not-sign-istanbul-convention.a181484/&quot; alt=&quot;combating violence against women and domestic violence&quot; /&gt; interesting. The reasoning is a bit weird for me, but not unreasonable. What’s really odd, is the convention itself. I’m just gonna pick out some parts that strike me as strange, not everything in the 37 pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;1 The purposes of this Convention are to:
a protect women against all forms of violence, and prevent, prosecute and eliminate violence against women and domestic violence;
b contribute to the elimination of all forms of discrimination against women and promote substantive equality between women and men, including by empowering women;
c design a comprehensive framework, policies and measures for the protection of and assistance to all victims of violence against women and domestic violence;
d promote international co-operation with a view to eliminating violence against women and domestic violence;
e provide support and assistance to organisations and law enforcement agencies to effectively co-operate in order to adopt an integrated approach to eliminating violence against women and domestic violence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most notably, every purpose of this convention has women (in this case broader used for everyone female) as primary victims and not men. Domestic violence isn’t an issue that needs to be tackled for one sex specifically. It doesn’t matter if you’re male or female or your partner is male or female, as soon as it happens, whoever is attacked is the victim. You might as well say “we’ll help anyone who experiences domestic violence in their family” and the outcome wouldn’t change much for women. Why not address everyone affected? Why not help everyone?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;1 Parties shall take the necessary measures to promote changes in the social and cultural patterns of behaviour of women and men with a view to eradicating prejudices, customs, traditions and all other practices which are based on the idea of the inferiority of women or on stereotyped roles for women and men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s almost hilarious how this comes soon after the purpose of the convention. I’m all in for tearing down some stereotypes. Let’s start with “men are inherently more violent” that this convention indirectly promotes. 
Sadly it’s not that easy. Through having testosterone in their body, men are in fact more aggressive. But not every man is aggressive or violent.&lt;br /&gt;
On top of that, you can’t just change stereotypes like that. It’s a social progress that spans over generations. Personally I think, I grew up in a very equal environment. I, just like others around me, don’t think of women as inferior. That’s what we’re gonna tell our daughters: Do what you want! 
But you can’t change the opinion of a grown adult through legislation. As much as some would like to do that, that’s hardly possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;2 Parties shall take the necessary legislative and other measures to prevent all forms of violence covered by the scope of this Convention by any natural or legal person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prevent violence? How? You can’t punish anyone who didn’t commit a crime in our legal systems. If they are violent, they’ve already commited the crime and you can’t prevent it. To prevent something, you have to take actions to not let it happen, like using a condom during intercourse. That however is impossible in case of violence, because it is actively conducted by someone. 
You can’t prevent an attack, be it in a family, between nations in forms of the declaration of war or in virtual space via hacking. You also can’t build a wall of some sorts between the two parties in a familiar relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;4 Parties shall take the necessary measures to encourage all members of society, especially men and boys, to contribute actively to preventing all forms of violence covered by the scope of this Convention.
5 Parties shall ensure that culture, custom, religion, tradition or so-called “honour” shall not be considered as justification for any acts of violence covered by the scope of this Convention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, we have the human rights, they already cover all forms of violence. Furthermore the 5th paragraph is pretty much moot in the same sense as these human rights, among pretty much every democratic constitution or whatever acts as their substitute, outlaw violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;1 Parties shall take, where appropriate, the necessary steps to include teaching material on issues such as equality between women and men, non-stereotyped gender roles, mutual respect, non-violent conflict resolution in interpersonal relationships, gender-based violence against women and the right to personal integrity, adapted to the evolving capacity of learners, in formal curricula and at all levels of education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally something sensible. It isn’t really odd, but I still wanted to highlight it. This should be at the core of our actions. Buildung an understanding, fighting violence, tear down social stigmas. But please also don’t replace them with new ones. If a woman decides to work to feed her family or be the breadwinner in the family, fine. If the woman decides to be a simple housewife, because the earnings of the man are enough, fine. Don’t condemn women who feel comfortable in traditional gender roles, it’s their decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;2 Parties shall provide or arrange for specialist women’s support services to all women victims of violence and their children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where’s the man’s support? Just because men experience it way less doesn’t mean they don’t need it. In fact, they’re currently in more need than women, because they lack these kinds of services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly enough, the occurance rate of “woman” in this convention thins out quickly after the a few pages. They’re still indirectly mentioned by the term “scope of this Convention” though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t really see the point of this convention though. Domestic violence has been an issue even 20 years ago. At least in Germany, a lot has been done to help women who experienced violence. It’s nothing new. It may be new in Asian countries, basically those east of Istanbul, but not so much in the West. I can really see Latvia’s point, as it condemn men more than it help women in most european countries.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Latvia isn’t gonna sign a new convention interesting. The reasoning is a bit weird for me, but not unreasonable. What’s really odd, is the convention itself. I’m just gonna pick out some parts that strike me as strange, not everything in the 37 pages.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Divide and Conquer</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Divide-And-Conquer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Divide and Conquer" /><published>2017-05-21T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-05-21T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Divide-And-Conquer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Divide-And-Conquer/">&lt;p&gt;I kinda presume everyone is familiar with the term and its meaning already. It’s one of the most famous strategies for leading a nation, a strategy to shift the attention of the general population away from politics by distracting them with each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I just want to do here is make a list on my own. I just wanna write down what I can come up with. Which groups speak up against others. For that I’m gonna first name the group and then list the things they’re against, hoping it’s at least somewhat comprehensive. It’s also notable, that I won’t concentrate on one country. I’m from Germany, so I feel more confident about the people living here, but some movements also exist elsewhere while others only exist in one country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Antifa&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; As the name implies, Antifascists are against fascists, although that’s a very broad statement as “fascist” in this sense isn’t how an historian would define it, but how an antifascist defines it. In that sense, it can mean a lot of things. A populist (see Trump), someone who speaks out against immigrants or even &lt;img src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=plyC2ipo2B4&amp;amp;t=0s&quot; alt=&quot;someone who wants to have this right to speak&quot; /&gt;. 
  Also included are bankers or the (finance-)capitalism as a whole, the own government with their police as their executive force. Also mainstream media&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Alt-rights&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (Illegal) immigrants, foreigners in general, political correctness, feminism, identity and gender politics. Also often times against mainstream media&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Black Lives Matter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Originally starting as a movement against police brutality, it quickly also included equality for blacks as a whole. As such it’s against white supremacists (especially in the police), alt-rights.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Young&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; This one’s probably not as profound as the ones above, but Brexit already indicated some kind of clash between generations. Millenials are sometimes deemed as stupid by baby boomers or vice versa. They also don’t find much representation in their democratic system.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Old&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; See the new generation as spoiled kids who basically fused with their phones.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feminists&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The patriarchy, sometimes those who use politically incorrect language. Depending on the feminist it can also include TERFs or men in general. Similarly to antifas, their definition of the others (here patriarchy) can be very broad, so are their opponents.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gender Identity Advocates&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Although similar to feminists at times, the topics are a bit different. Generally against conservativs who’re against their believe. It can include those who refuse certain pronouns or identities.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Free Speech Advocates&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; A relatively young, barely established group of people who don’t agree with politically correct language or langauge police in general. Can also include right-wing people who lost the ability to reasonably voice their opinion on a some subjects.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Working Class&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Probably one of the oldest groups here and a very moody one. Oftentimes being against what the TV is showing. That can include terrorists, sexual offenders, immigrants, people who live on welfare or a scandalous company.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Greens&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Those running nuclear power plants or subsidising their use.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And most importantly the ones that have to be distracted from:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Rich&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Basically everyone who doesn’t earn millions or above per year or month. Or to quote Warren Buffet: “It’s class warfare. My class is winning, but they shouldn’t be.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Poor&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Anyone in power, be it politically, financially or economically. I’m not sure if they know though.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I kinda presume everyone is familiar with the term and its meaning already. It’s one of the most famous strategies for leading a nation, a strategy to shift the attention of the general population away from politics by distracting them with each other.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Clear Language</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Clear-Language/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Clear Language" /><published>2017-05-07T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-05-07T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Clear-Language</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Clear-Language/">&lt;p&gt;This article is basically a follow up on this &lt;img src=&quot;http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2017/05/transracialism-article-controversy.html&quot; alt=&quot;article&quot; /&gt; and this &lt;img src=&quot;https://twitter.com/transscribe/status/860576433059639299&quot; alt=&quot;tweet&quot; /&gt; as well as the discussion to that tweet afterwards. Here I want to clarify why this tweet is just wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;By looking at your placement of Tuvel’s career over my safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off all this comparison is lacking very much. On the one side, we have the career of the author of the very article being discussed. The outcome of this discussion could very well influence parts of her career. As seen with Jordan B. Peterson who recently got his &lt;img src=&quot;http://dailysignal.com/2017/04/03/politically-incorrect-professor-gets-denied-grant-funding/&quot; alt=&quot;funding cut&quot; /&gt; after he repeatedly spoken up against gender pronouns and similiar topics, it’s not too far-fetched. On the other hand we have singular person who has no direct connection to the topic at hand - except being on the other side of the debate as a transgender person. It’s completely blown out of proportion to compare these two. The scientific paper is only of lesser interest to most people especially as it’s behind a $50 paywall. So only those who actively pay attention to this debate. Its effect in the general population is insignificant at best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly, the tweet is extremely misleading as it uses “safety”, a word used for the physical well-being of a human. It’s either blatantly exaggerating the effect of that paper or just plainly used incorrectly. For the first case it means that paper is threatening her physically in some form. But as I explained above its effect is insignificant, so that’s highly unlikely. She can be scared of Trump’s executive orders or new laws being passed. These might change the country in such a way, that she could feel unsafe. But this is a scientific paper read by a very small community. Words are powerful, so they can still change some behaviour or opinions in its readers, which may effect her. However as we live in free democracies with free speech, that’s a non-argument, as this its purpose to some degree. I agree that we should strive to become a peaceful community where everyone is at least tolerated if not accepted, but the path to that is unknown to us, so we have to find it ourselves. For that we need to discuss these things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the second case, she uses the powerful word “safety” to describe something entirely different to her. That can be confusing for a moment and incredibly bad in the long run. Language is a powerful tool. It gives us the ability to communicate, to transfer information to one another. But to properly use this powerful tool it also needs to be well-defined. Here Burns uses “safety” while &lt;em&gt;probably&lt;/em&gt; meaning something a lot minor. On top of that she expresses something subjective, something that isn’t measurable. She only feel less safe. Safety while not being entirely measurable, is least visible. We feel unsafe near carnivorous animals or unstable constructions. We also feel more safe if we’re with a group of friends at night in a city. Not to mention, I can’t even be sure what she means, since the original meaning makes no sense in this context. So I have to guess its meaning and to what degree it’s used. Hence why I used probably probably in the sentence above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily it doesn’t make much difference here, because it didn’t evolve into a discussion. Regardless these cases weakens our ability to communicate. Language is just a tool to transform and transfer our thoughts to others. If some don’t use this tool properly, bend words as they want, it becomes dull. We wouldn’t be able to communicate properly as we have to guess the intention behind some words. It would disrupt discussions or in the worst case, make it impossible to understand others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly I was asked why I felt entitled to reply to that tweet. Unfortunately, I haven’t figured out how to embed tweets with markdown, so just gonna quote them one after another. For reference, the last part of the discussion starts &lt;img src=&quot;https://twitter.com/williampietri/status/861227432912617472&quot; alt=&quot;here&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you are jumping in to bother a marginalized person about your desire for her meeting your standard of precision&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Bother” is aharsh word here. Twitter (to some degree) exists to voice your own opinion on a variety of topics. Nothing says I can’t put my comment under that of any person. Rather it’s the other way around. Since we live in democracies, it should be encouraged to express your opinion and challenge those of others.
Besides, why am I bothered by a thread of more than 34 replies? Just because I’m a white man doesn’t mean you can bother me more than others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus as I pointed out above, this standard may very well be more important to me than the arbitary “safety” of Ms. Burns, a person I just don’t know. Of course the things I value are more important to me than the things others value. Now, before I get a reply that I don’t care for someone else’s safety. I don’t want her to be unsafe, but her claim that she’s less safe because of that paper is completely empty. There is nothing that warrents that feeling of insecurity, so I don’t see why I should put my standard of precision beneath her felt safety&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Because you personally believe it doesn’t fit right. But why does that entitle you to contradict and/or bother her?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, that’s what it means to freely speak your mind. If I see something that doesn’t fit, I’m free to point that out. I’m also free to not do so for that matter. That’s a right in every western democracy and the very system we live on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Why do you believe your reaction is so much more important?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nowhere did I say so. This is just the impression you, Mr. Pietri, have of me. My reaction or opinion doesn’t need to be more or less important to qualify as a response to that of someone else.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This article is basically a follow up on this and this as well as the discussion to that tweet afterwards. Here I want to clarify why this tweet is just wrong.</summary></entry></feed>